harkins.com 2019-10-15

# Privacy Policy :: Harkins Theatres

## Privacy Policy

### PRIVACY POLICY

Thank you for visiting Harkins Theatres and reviewing our Privacy Policy Statement. We are providing you this Privacy Policy Statement to inform you about the information that could be collected online as a result of visiting or requesting a service, how that information will be used, and what steps are taken to ensure the security of customer data. Your rights to privacy are of utmost importance to Harkins Theatres. Your trust and confidence when conducting business with us through the Internet is equally important. Harkins Theatres has created this privacy policy to describe its information gathering and privacy practices. This Privacy Policy is designed to protect your personal information, while permitting us to provide you the opportunity to obtain obtain useful information, products and services and to participate in online contests or promotions. You are never obligated to provide us any personal information, and if at any time you no longer wish to receive communications from Harkins Theatres, you may "opt out" of receiving these communications at any time. Your use of this website constitutes acceptance of this Privacy Policy and any other applicable terms.

### COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

In order to register to receive information, products or services available through our website, or to permit us to respond to your inquiries or become eligible for online contests, our site's registration or entry forms may require that you provide basic contact information (name and e-mail address), demographic information (like your ZIP code or age), financial information (like account or credit card numbers) and/or lifestyle related information (like movie type preferences). Contests or promotions on our site may require contact information and demographic information to be eligible for participation. We may also collect the Internet Protocol address and e-mail address of visitors to our web site, the e-mail addresses of those who post messages to a bulletin board, and the e-mail addresses of those who desire to communicate with us via e-mail.

We do not share information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes unless you affirmatively agree to such disclosure - typically by opting in to receive information from a third party that is participating in a sweepstakes or other promotion on one of our websites. If you do not want your information to be used by a third party for direct marketing purposes (or other purposes unrelated to the uses described herein), do not opt in to such use by that third party. Please note that if you opt in to receive direct marketing from a third party, your information will be subject to that party's privacy policy. If you later decide that you do not want that third party to use your information, you will need to contact that third party directly. We recommend that you review the privacy policy of any party that collects your information to determine how that entity will handle your information.

At any time you may opt-out of receiving marketing communications from us or request that we not provide your personal contact, demographic, and/or lifestyle-related information to third parties. Please see the information below regarding opting out.

### OPT-OUT - TO REMOVE YOUR NAME AND INFORMATION FROM OUR LISTS

You have the choice to opt-out of receiving marketing communications from us. You can also change or modify information previously provided. You may opt out by e-mailing our customer service department at optout@harkinstheatres.com. In addition, if you would like to contact us regarding this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your interaction with this site, please write us at:

Harkins Enterprises  
7511 East McDonald Drive  
Scottsdale, AZ 85250

### ONLINE CUSTOMER SERVICE AND ALTERNATIVES

Harkins Theatres offers access to its information online that you might otherwise request in person. Our goal is to provide guests with a more convenient and efficient means in which to interact with us. If at any time you choose not to proceed with a transaction offered online, your choice will in no way affect your ability to receive benefits or services another way. If you prefer to request information from us in person, you may still do so at our office.

### COLLECTION AND USE OF INFORMATION

**Information Collected and Stored Automatically by Cookies**  
We may use "cookies" to gather information during your visit. The web server that hosts the Harkins Theatres site gathers certain information about the visit automatically in a standard log file. This information never identifies you personally and consists of only the following items:

The Internet domain (for example, "xcompany.com" if you use a private Internet access account, or "yourschool.edu" if you connect from a university's domain) from which you access the website; The IP address (an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web) from which you access the website; and the date and time of your access.

We use this information to gather statistics about the amount of use the site receives. Again, we do not automatically record information about you as an individual. This automatically recorded information is not shared, sold, or otherwise disseminated by Harkins Theatres.

When, from time to time, you opt in to an online service feature offered by Harkins Theatres, use of cookies is limited to the minimum function necessary to prevent duplication of results from any particular website. A cookie is only transmitted at the time you submit your service request to us and consists of a unique text string to be stored on your computer and only retrieved in the event that you voluntarily return to the relevant page. You can always avoid receiving the cookie by not submitting the service request to us. You can also refuse the cookie or delete the cookie file from your computer system by selecting various options on your computer's operating system. Refer to your browser's help facility for the specific instructions about deleting, disabling, or refusing cookies.

**Information Collected From Children**  
Though Harkins Theatres does not specifically request information from children, we would comply with any request for compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Policy Protection Act of 1998 ("COPPA"), requiring parental consent before we collected any personal information from an individual under the age of 13. The text of COPPA is available at <http://www.ftc.gov/ogc/coppa1.htm>.

### SECURITY

Harkins Theatres and its partners have taken several steps to safeguard the integrity of its computer systems and networks. These steps include, but are not limited to, individual authentication, the security of transmitted data, security monitoring, auditing, and encryption of information. Security methods and measures have been integrated into the design, implementation and day-to-day practices of the entire Harkins Theatres website.

### EXTERNAL LINKS DISCLAIMER

Harkins Theatres web pages contain links to various other websites operated by other parties not under our control. When you link to another site, you are no longer on the Harkins Theatres site and this Privacy Statement will not apply to such other sites. When you link to another website, you are subject to the privacy policy of that new site. Links to websites outside of Harkins Theatres are offered solely for your convenience. Harkins Theatres is not responsible for and does not have control over the policies or content of any third-party sites.

Neither Harkins Theatres, nor any agency, officer, employee, or contractor of Harkins Theatres warrants the accuracy, reliability, or timeliness of any information published by this system, nor endorses any content, viewpoints, products, or services linked from this system, and shall not be held liable for any losses caused by reliance on the accuracy, reliability or timeliness of such information. Portions of such information may be inaccurate or outdated. Any person or entity that relies on any information obtained from this system does so at his or her own risk.

### PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT IS SUBJECT TO CHANGE

This policy may be updated or revised from time to time, so please check back periodically in order to receive advance notice of any substantive changes to the manner in which the information you disclose on this website may be collected, used, or disseminated.

### CONTACT INFORMATION

To offer comments about the Harkins Theatres website, or about the information presented in any of the foregoing terms of use, including the privacy policy, please [contact us.](http://harkins.develop/index.php?cID=447)

If you choose to provide us with personal information - by filling out our form with your personal information and submitting it to us from this website - we use that information to respond to your message and to help us get you the information you have requested or register your opinion. We only share the information you provide with another organization if your inquiry relates to that organization, or as otherwise required by law. Any comments collected are themselves subject to the protections of the privacy policy.

### LIMITATION OF LIABILITY

Under no circumstances shall Harkins Theatres or its affiliates be liable for any punitive, incidental, direct, indirect, accidental, special or consequential damages that may result from the use of this website. This limitation applies whether the alleged liability is based on negligence, contract, tort, strict liability or any other legal theory, even if Harkins Theatres has been notified of the possibility of such damages. In the event some jurisdictions do not allow the exclusion or limitation of incidental or consequential damages, Harkins Theatres' liability in such jurisdictions shall be limited to the extent permitted by law.

### INDEMNIFICATION

You agree to defend, indemnify and hold harmless Harkins Theatres, its affiliates, and their respective employees, contractors, agents, officers, and directors from all liabilities, claims, and expenses (including reasonable attorneys' fees) that arise out of or are related to any user content you submit, post, transmit or make available through the website, your violation of this Agreement, or your violation of any third party rights.
